carbonrally.com 2012-05-23

# Carbonrally – climate change community focused on fun, social, and competitive challenges

Carbonrally.com recognizes the importance of protecting information collected from you through our web site. **We will not knowingly share your email address or any other personally identifiable information with any marketing companies under any circumstances.** Further, we have adopted a privacy policy described below. Carbonrally.com will comply with this policy, and any applicable privacy-related law, when we gather information from users of the site. This policy is current as of October 15, 2007. This policy may change, and you should check this area of the site from time to time to obtain the most current version of this policy.

**Information We Collect**

_Your Personal Profile information_. We collect information including your email address, zip code, personal description, user icon and demographic category that you enter during the registration process.

_Your Challenge Activity_. We collect information regarding your Challenge activity on the site. This includes the history of Challenges you accept and un-accept, and any Challenge ideas you submit or vote on in the Challenge Workshop area of the site.

_Your Commentary_. We collect comments and content you post in the Challenge, Team, City, My Carbon, Challenge Workshop, and Blog areas of the site.

_Usage Logs_. In some cases we may collect information on how you use the site. This may include a log of the pages you view, the features you use, and the time and duration of these activities.

**Information We Use and Disclose**

In general, Carbonrally.com uses the personal information collected to provide services and communicate with you. To this end, we use the information to notify you of new Featured Challenges, track your CO2 reduction progress, facilitate communication among site members, and to facilitate discussions and team management.

We will only share personal information that you provide outside the public areas of the site under the following circumstances:

– When you consent or explicitly direct Carbonrally.com to share the information.

– When you choose to send a Private Message (email) to another Carbonrally member, your email address will be exposed to the recipient. A warning that this will occur appears during the private messaging process.

– When Carbonrally has a reasonable belief that disclosure of personal information is required to abide by laws and regulations; to investigate violations of our Terms of Service; or to protect the rights and safety of Carbonrally, its users, or the public.

We may share with third parties aggregate information or information that does not personally identify individuals.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Carbonrally.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13.

Questions about the privacy practices of Carbonrally.com should be directed via email to feedback at carbonrally.com
